(Sheldon:)Now, sit down.
"I call your attention
to the events of November 16th.
Do you remember that date?"
"Darn tooting, I do.
(Penny(reading):)If the court will excuse my homespun,
corn-fed, Nebraskan turn of phrase."
(Sheldon:)-Excellent. Go on.
-"The reason that date is, like...
(Penny:)...so totally fixed in my memory is that
I had the privilege to be witness...
(Penny:)...to one of the most heroic acts
I've ever seen in, like, ever."
"And who performed that heroic act?"
"Why, you did, sir.
You, Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
(Penny:)And may I add,
it is a privilege to know you."
"There's no need for compliments.
This court is only interested in the facts."
"But it is a fact
that it's a privilege to know you.
Totally."
"A teardrop rolls down my cheek"?